export const elmPrepMvmt = [{
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Mrs. Smith is driving _________ the tunnel.",
        "options": [
            "through",
            "down",
            "off",
            "up"
        ],
        "answer": "through"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "David is about to fall _________ a rock.",
        "options": [
            "to",
            "off",
            "down",
            "from"
        ],
        "answer": "off"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Mr. Cook is going _________ the tent to get some sleep.",
        "options": [
            "into",
            "through",
            "down",
            "out of"
        ],
        "answer": "into"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "They went _________ the movie theater.",
        "options": [
            "over",
            "down",
            "to",
            "from"
        ],
        "answer": "to"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "I was unable to get _________ her grasp.",
        "options": [
            "over",
            "rom",
            "down",
            "out of"
        ],
        "answer": "out of"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "I started to climb the stairs _________ the bottom.",
        "options": [
            "through",
            "from",
            "out of",
            "down"
        ],
        "answer": "from"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Luis climbed _________ the mountain stairs.",
        "options": [
            "to",
            "up",
            "from",
            "out of"
        ],
        "answer": "up"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Tears were flowing _________ her cheeks.",
        "options": [
            "up",
            "from",
            "down",
            "out of"
        ],
        "answer": "down"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Angela was _________ danger.",
        "options": [
            "out of",
            "from",
            "through",
            "down"
        ],
        "answer": "out of"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Luigi drove _________ a red light.",
        "options": [
            "out of",
            "from",
            "down",
            "through"
        ],
        "answer": "through"
    }
]